Hi, welcome to session 16,
嗨，欢迎来到第 16 节课，
in this session, we're going to talk about advanced strumming,
在这节课中，我们将讨论高级扫弦，
going beyond the normal rhythm, rhythms that you normally play.
超越你通常演奏的正常节奏。
We're talk about sixteenth notes,
我们谈论的是十六分音符，
a new concept for us, strumming sixteenth notes,
这是一个新概念，扫弦十六分音符，
as well as we're going to learn some cool rhythm techniques,
我们还将学习一些很酷的扫弦技巧，
that you can incorporate into your own playing.
你可以把它们融入你自己的演奏中。
In the guitar tips section,
在吉他技巧部分，
we're going to talk about acoustic guitars,
我们将谈论原声吉他，
different types of acoustic guitars,
不同类型的原声吉他，
steel string, nylon string, twelve string,
钢丝弦、尼龙弦、十二根弦，
we're going talk about some different equipment for acoustic playing,
我们将讨论一些不同的原声吉他弹奏设备，
if you use a lot of interested in using some effects with your acoustic,
如果你对原声吉他某些效果感兴趣，
pickups, processors, and how to manage feedback,
拾音器，处理器，如何管理反馈，
one of the worst things that an acoustic guitar player always finds himself in.
原声吉他演奏者总是发现的最糟糕的事情之一，
Okay, so let's go ahead and get started.
所以让我们继续并开始吧。
Now let's talk about sixteenth notes,
现在我们来谈谈十六分音符，
let's review our rhythms,
让我们复习一下我们的节奏，
we haven't talked about rhythms and wow, a whole bunch of sessions,
我们还没有讨论过节奏，一大堆的课程，
but let's talk about them for a second,
但是让我们来谈谈它们，
because we have one more level,
因为我们还有一个层次，
We still need to get down into, into rhythms,
我们仍然需要进入节奏，
whole notes get four beats,
全音符有四拍，
half notes get two beats.
二分音符有两拍，
quarter notes get one beat,
四分音符有一拍，
and then we split the atom there,
然后我们在那里分裂原子，
and we got into eighth notes,
我们得到八分音符，
two eighth notes equal one quarter note,
两个八分音符相当于一个四分音符，
two eighth notes for every beat,
两个八音符对应一拍，
and now we're going to go down one more level,
现在我们要再往下走一级，
to sixteenth notes,
到十六分音符，
so it takes four sixteenth notes to make up one beat,
所以需要四个十六分音符才能组成一拍，
I'm basically splitting an eighth note now,
我现在是拆分八分音符，
so now I have four sixteenth notes make up one beat,
所以我现在有四个十六分音符组成一拍，
so in a measure of 4/4 times,
所以，在 4/4 拍的小节中，
there would actually be sixteen,
它将是 16 ，
sixteenth notes would make up a measure in 4/4 time,
十六个音符可以在 4/4 拍中组成一个小节，
that's how you get the name,
这就是名字的由来，
wholes, halves, quarters, eighths and now sixteenth.
全，二分，四分，八分，现在是十六分。
There are division subdivisions lower than that,
还有比这更低的拆分，
thirty seconds, sixty fourth notes,
三十二分，六十四分音符，
but you as a guitar player,
但你作为一名吉他演奏者，
probably are never gonna see anything like that,
可能永远不会看到这样的事情，
I can probably count on my hand the times,
我可以用我的手数一数，
I've ever even seen a thirty second note,
我曾经见过的三十二分音符，
but you will be dealing with sixteenth notes quite a bit.
但你将会处理相当多的十六分音符。
Okay, so let's learn about those,
好的，让我们了解一下这些，
first, let's talk about it in in single notes before we get to chords,
首先，在我们开始和弦之前，我们先用单音符来讨论一下，
okay, so let's take a look at them,
好的，让我们先看一下它们，
in your right hand, you want to make sure you're doing down up, down up,
在你的右手，你要确保你做的是下上，下上，
you're alternating your picking.
你在轮换你的拨片。
So just on a C,
所以，在 C 中，
let's look at that first example there,
就让我们来看看第一个例子，
we have four quarter notes,
我们有四个四分音符，
and then another measure of that, and then we go into eighth notes
然后另一个小节，我们进入八分音符，
and then sixteenth notes,
然后是十六分音符，
ready, two, three,
准备， 2 3 ，
eighth notes, now, down,
八分音符，现在，下，
here come those sixteenth notes.
现在是十六分音符。
Good.
好的。
Now let's try it with a metronome,
现在让我们用节拍器来试一试，
two, ready go,
2 ，准备，开始，
quarter notes first,
首先是四分音符，
eighth notes,
八分音符，
sixteenth,
十六分音符，
good.
好的。
Let's do exercise number three
让我们做第三个练习，
and vary the notes up a little bit,
把音符稍微调高一点，
one, two, ready go,
1 2 ，准备，开始，
that's a little too fast,
这有点太快了，
let's slow that down,
让我们放慢一点，
go,
开始，
do it again, go.
再来一次，开始。
In sixteenth note strumming,
在十六分音符扫弦中，
there's two different ways that we can go about it,
我们有两种不同的方法，
and there's two different camps of people that learn this,
有两个不同阵营的人学习这个，
so let's see if which camp you're going to be in,
所以让我们看看你会在哪个阵营，
let me play this rhythm
让我演奏这个节奏，
and you try and play it back to me,
你试着把弹奏它给我听，
okay, I'll do it just on a G chord.
好的，我只用 G 和弦来做。
ready, go,
准备，开始，
good, now a small percentage of people can actually listen to the rhythm
好的，一小部分人可以听着节奏，
and just go, okay, I get it
然后说，好的，我明白了，
and they just suddenly start playing it,
他们突然开始演奏，
how they do that, I don't know,
他们是怎么做到的，我不知道，
it's one of the great mysteries of life in,
这是生命中最大的奥秘之一，
but it is a it is, it is a fact,
但它是一个事实，
that some people hear it
一些人听到了它，
and they can just understand it and process it,
他们就能理解它并处理它，
they don't even can tell you how they're learning it that way,
他们甚至不能告诉你他们是如何通过这种方式学习的，
but it's just one of those things now for the rest of us mere mortals,
但对于我们这些凡人来说，
that have to learn exactly what we're trying to do with these strumming,
我们必须确切地学习我们试图用这些扫弦做什么，
we're gonna go, I'm gonna take you through for about the next five minutes,
我将在接下来的五分钟里教你们，
how to get up to a complex rhythm like that,
如何达到像这样复杂的节奏，
we're going to start way back in the basics,
我们将从基础知识开始，
on a G chord, we're going to start doing eighth notes.
在 G 和弦上，我们将开始做八分音符。
Okay, so this is sixteenth note strumming exercise,
好的，这是十六分音符扫弦练习，
this is the first part of it,
这是它的第一部分，
let's just do number one,
让我们做第一个，
we're going somewhere with all this [],
我们要去每个地方，
let's, just hang with me on this,
在这件事上跟着我，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
down up, down up, down up, down up,
下上，下上，下上，下上，
again, down, up, down, slow it down a little bit.
再来一次，下上，下，慢一点。
Now let's take a look at number two,
现在让我们来看看第二个，
now I threw in some sixteenth notes,
现在我加入一些十六分音符，
the key is keeping your wrist loose,
关键是让你的手腕放松，
it's almost like you're flicking something off of your hand,
就像你在从你的手中弹出什么东西，
remember, we described that earlier, when we were doing rhythms,
还记得我们之前在练习节奏的时候描述过的吗，
it's like you're flicking something off of your hand,
就像你在弹你手上的东西一样，
number two, ready, go,
第二个，准备，开始，
down up, down up down up, down up down up, down,
下上，下上下上，下上下上，下，
eighth, sixteenth.
八分音符，十六分音符。
Good, number three, go.
好的，第三个，开始。
Got it,
明白了吗，
okay, now let's put all sixteenth notes in a row,
好的，现在我们把所有的十六分音符排成一排，
so just gonna be sixteen sixteenth notes,
所以只有十六分、十六分音符，
ready go,
准备，开始，
see how that works,
看到这是如何工作的，
now I want you to try an accent
现在我要你试一试重音，
or give a little extra emphasis the first sixteenth in every one of those four pairs,
或者特别强调每四个中的第一个十六分音符，
okay, 4/4 sets of four,
好的， 4/4 拍中的四个，
in the first sixteenth notes, in each of those,
在第一个十六分音符，
I want you to try an accent,
我想让你试一试重音，
okay, so it'll be something like this,
好的，应该是这样的，
How we note that musically is,
我们在乐谱上标记的是，
you'll see that little sideways V sign over that first sixteenth note,
你会在第一个十六分音符上看到一个小的侧向 V 符号，
that's telling you to accent it.
它告诉你要重音它。
Now don't just play it louder,
现在不要只是把声音放得大一些，
make the other one softer,
让另一个声音柔和一些，
there's only so loud that you can play,
只有这么大的声音，你能演奏，
okay, so make the other one softer and really bring out that first one.
好的，让另一个更柔和，把第一个拿出来。
Let's do it again, ready, go.
让我们再来一次，准备，开始。
Good, keep that wrist loose,
好的，保持手腕放松，
hold that pick nice and steady,
拿稳拨片，
okay, works out best to have a little bit of a flexibility in your pick,
好的，最好是在你的拨片上有一点灵活性，
not too thick of a pick when you're doing these.
当你这样做的时候不要拨片太多。
Okay, look at strumming exercise number two there,
好了，看看第二个扫弦练习，
now I'm gonna put those accents in different places,
现在我要把这些重音放在不同的地方，
okay, let's do that together,
好的，让我们一起来做，
ready go,
准备，开始，
so I'm doing it every other one there.
我在做每隔一个（重音）。
Okay.
好的。
Now, let's look at exercise number three,
现在，我们看第三个练习，
now I have it on the first sixteenth note and the fourth sixteenth note,
现在我把它写在第一个十六分音符和第四个十六分音符上，
so I have my first up stroke accent
所以我有我的第一个向上重音，
and it changes the pattern a little bit and you have to get used to it,
它有点改变了模式，你必须适应它，
I'll do it real slow, ready, go,
我会慢慢来的，准备，开始，
down up, down up, down up,
下上，下上，下上，
see how that works.
看到这是怎么工作的。
Now for the next couple of minutes,
在接下来的几分钟里，
it's gonna sound really stupid
这听起来真的很愚蠢，
to anybody who's listening to this that's not playing guitar,
对于任何听这个却没有弹吉他的人来说，
because when you're actually working with a guitar,
因为当你真正使用吉他的时候，
you'll know exactly what I'm talking about,
你会确切地知道我在说什么，
but if somebody's just walking through the room,
但如果有人只是在房间里走来走去，
they're gonna think you're nuts,
他们会认为你是傻瓜，
as we start talking about downs and ups,
当我们开始谈论下上时，
so just bear with this,
所以就忍着点这个，
let's go to the next exercise with that.
让我们来做下一个练习。
Okay, now, I've got it on the first, the fourth one
好的，现在我把它放在第一个，第四个，
and then also on what is that, the seventh one as well,
然后也在第七个，
so it would be something like this, ready, go,
所以它是这样的，准备，开始，
down up, down, down up, down, down up, down, down up,
下上，下，下上，下，下上，下，下上，
just keep doing it, really make the most of the accents.
继续做，最大限度地利用重音。
Okay, now let's play exercise number five,
好的，现在让我们来做第五个练习，
for this one, I'm going turn on my handy dandy metronome,
对于这个，我要打开我的节拍器，
and he's clicking off sixteenth notes,
它在弹出十六分音符，
So it may sound like it's going real fast,
所以这听起来可能很快，
but it's actually he's gonna be clicking off sixteenth notes,
但实际上它要弹出十六分音符，
so we're actually a good bit slower than we than we were for the previous example,
所以我们实际上比前面的例子慢了很多，
because there's some tricky accents in this,
因为这里面有一些微妙的重音，
let's go through it,
让我们来一遍，
one, two, ready, down up, ready, go,
1 2 ，准备，下上，准备，开始，
down up, down up, down up, down up,
下上，下上，下上，下上
down up, down up, down up, down up, down up, down up,
下上，下上，下上，下上，下上，下上，
okay, so nice and fast would be something like this,
好的，快一点会像这样，
see how that works.
看到这是怎么回事了吗。
Now, I'm going to take out the ones that we were not accenting,
现在我要把没有重音的拿走，
so all I'm left with is the accented ones.
所以我只剩下有重音的那些。
Okay, now here's a big concept,
好的，现在有个重要的概念，
I want you to keep your hand going,
我希望你保持你的手运动，
even though you're not actually playing those non-accented notes,
即使你没有在弹奏那些非重音的音符，
so you can end up only thing you're being playing now
这样你现在可以只弹奏，
is the down up, down up, down, down up, down,
也就是下上，下上，下，下上，下，
well, you may think to yourself,
你可能会想，
well, I get it,
好的，我明白了，我可以往下走，往下走，然后以正确的节奏演奏。不，不会成功的，对吧？你必须让你的手仍然做第十六个音符，下，上，下。
I can just go down, down and just play it at the right rhythm,
我可以下下，然后以正确的节奏演奏，
no, it won't work out, right,
不，不会成功的，
you got to get your hand still doing sixteenth notes,
你必须让你的手仍然做十六分音符，
down up down up, down up down up,
下上下上，下上下上，
for it to work okay.
让它工作，好吗。
Let's try that rhythm,
让我们试试这种节奏，
it would be rhythm number six,
这将是第六个节奏（练习），
all I did was take out the unaccented notes,
我所做的就是拿出没有重音的音符，
looks a little different written on paper, but it's the same rhythm,
写在纸上看起来有点不同，但节奏是一样的，
okay, you ready, go,
好的，准备，开始，
see what I did there,
看到我在那里做了什么吗，
try one more time, a little bit slower,
再试一次，慢一点，
two, ready go,
2 ，准备，开始，
keep that hand going,
保持手的移动，
now in the last rhythm there,
现在在最后一个节奏中，
it just adds a couple of sixteenth notes at the end,
它只是在结尾增加了几个十六分音符，
now, I don't want you to worry too much about the rhythm,
现在，我不想让你太担心节奏，
Let's not look at the music for a second,
让我们暂时不要看音乐，
I want you to do the same rhythm.
我想让你做同样的节奏。
Okay, ready, go,
好的，准备，开始，
the last rhythm adds those two sixteenth notes at the end,
最后一段节奏在结尾处加上了那两个十六分音符，
so be something like this,
所以就像这样，
ready, go, now,
准备，开始，
let's see if we can start it together,
让我们看看我们是否可以一起开始，
start, go.
开始。
Okay, that's a little bit about sixteenth note strums,
好的，这是一点关于十六分音符扫弦，
now it's easy for me to explain,
现在我很容易解释了，
it does take a good while if you don't feel it naturally to, to go through them,
如果你不自然地感觉到，经历它们确实需要一段很长的时间，
so my advice is go slow,
因此，我的建议是，慢慢来，
don't get too lost in the downs and the ups,
不要太迷失在下上之中。
okay, I know that's what you're concentrating on now,
好的，我知道这就是你现在关注的问题，
once you kind of got the rhythm, get away from that
一旦你掌握了节奏，就远离它，
and just remember, keep your hand going, keep that wrist nice and loose.
记住，保持你的手移动，保持手腕的柔韧和放松。
Good strumming technique involves a couple of things,
好的扫弦技巧包括几件事，
keeping our wrist loose,
保持手腕放松，
gripping our pick nice and strong
紧握我们的拨片，
and having a pick that's got a little bit of flexibility in it,
并拥有一个有一点灵活性的拨片，
okay, do you don't want to use a pick that's too thick.
好的，你不想用太厚的拨片。
Okay, look at your next exercise there
好的，看看你的下一个练习，
and let's see if we can use our new strumming pattern, sixteenth strumming pattern,
让我们看看是否可以使用我们的新的扫弦模式，十六分扫弦模式，
going through these different chords.
通过这些不同的和弦。
Okay, a G, Em, a C and a D,
好的， G Em C D ，
starts on a G, ready go.
从 G 开始，准备，开始。
Good, now, there's some other techniques that I use,
好的，我也会使用一些其他的技巧，
when I'm playing acoustic stuff as well,
当我弹奏原声吉他时，
one of them, I don't know what to call it,
其中之一，我不知道该怎么称呼它，
it's just kind of you're muting your whole all of your strings while strumming,
这是一种你在扫弦时，把所有的弦都静音，
and just gonna gets a real kind of a chunk sound,
然后就会得到一种真正的[块状]声音，
okay, so if I'm on a G,
好的，如果我在 G 上，
it'd be something like this,
它会是这样的，
let me just demonstrate it first,
让我先演示一下，
see what I'm doing there,
看到我在那里做了什么吗，
if I go through real slowly,
如果我走得很慢，
my hand is coming down,
我的手下来，
I'm muting it with my left hand,
我在用我的左手静音，
completely covering the strings,
完全盖住了琴弦，
so I'm hitting the strings and palm muting at the same time,
所以我同时敲击琴弦和手掌静音，
so as soon as I hit the strings,
所以我一按下琴弦，
I'm muting them,
我就把它们调成静音，
I don't even have to have anything going on with my left hand,
我的左手甚至不需要出任何事情，
I can still do it,
我还是能做到，
I'm coming through and I'm muting it with my palm immediately,
我下来，马上用手掌静音，
sometimes it's really helpful to get a good rhythm exercise going like that,
有时候，像这样做一个好的节奏练习真的很有帮助，
using the chunking,
使用[组块]，
I want to call it,
我想称呼它，
using that chunk in there makes you gives your rhythm, playing a little bit more excitement.
在那里使用块会让你的节奏变得更刺激。
Okay, you also can do muting,
好的，你也可以静音，
even doing when you're doing chords,
甚至在和弦的时候也可以，
so like let's say I'm doing my power chord again,
比如我又弹强力和弦，
so if I'm on F, I can go something like,
所以，如果我是 F ，我可以这样，
accenting the first of each,
重音每个的第一个，
let's say I don't want to really be strumming full up,
比如，我不想全部扫弦上，
I can still use that mute technique,
我仍然可以使用那个静音技巧，
here's another key,
这是另一个关键，
if I want to strum, but I don't want to be very loud,
如果我想扫弦，但我不想太大声，
I want to be kind of quiet about my strumming,
我想对我的扫弦保持安静，
notice my pick is not down like that,
注意我的拨片不是那样向下的，
I slowly shift it sideways,
我慢慢地把它移到一边，
I'm playing with almost the side of the pick,
我几乎在拨片的一边弹奏，
it a little bit softer sound,
声音稍微轻了一点，
I'm still able to strum,
我还是能扫弦，
but I'm able to get a softer sound with it.
但我可以用它发出更柔和的声音。
All right, let's talk about some different types of guitars,
好了，让我们来谈谈不同类型的吉他，
okay, there's very couple of standard, different sizes of guitars,
好的，有几把标准的、不同大小的吉他，
let's talk about acoustic guitars sizes first,
让我们先来谈谈原声吉他的尺寸，
there basically three different sizes you're going to see,
基本上你会看到三种不同的尺寸，
one of them is called a dreadnought,
其中一个被称为 dreadnought ，
think of it as small, medium and large,
把它想象成小的、中的和大的，
medium, it's going to be a dreadnought size guitar,
中的，这将是一把 dreadnought 大小的吉他，
this is a dreadnought guitar,
这是一把 dreadnought 吉他，
okay, has to do with the size of the body,
好的，和身体的大小有关，
it's pretty much standard size,
这差不多是标准尺寸，
you'll also see jumbo,
你还会看到 jumbo ，
okay, that would be your big,
那就是你最大的，
okay, slightly larger, slightly thicker in the back as well,
稍微大一点，后背也稍微厚一点，
gets a little bit more bass sound,
得到更多一点的低音，
still tune the same,
仍然是一样的调子，
so it's not a pitch thing,
所以这不是音高的问题，
it's just a little bit of a fuller sound,
这只是一点更饱满的声音，
it is bigger though.
不过，它更大一点。
Okay, next one is kind of a concert size guitar,
好的，下一个是 concert 大小的吉他，
which is a little bit smaller than this,
比这个小一点，
okay, you'll also see sometimes,
你有时也会看到，
a cutaway in a guitar,
吉他上的一个切面，
which will be, so this little part of the guitar is cutaway,
吉他的这一小部分就被切掉了，
so you can actually get up here to the higher frets on a normal acoustic guitars.
所以你可以在这里用普通的原声吉他达到更高的音阶。
Now let's talk about different types of acoustic guitar,
现在让我们来谈谈不同类型的原声吉他，
okay, here's a steel string guitar,
好的，这是一把钢弦吉他，
good for country stuff,
很适合乡村的东西，
good for regular old rhythm playing,
适合有规律的老节奏演奏，
sitting around the living room singing songs with friends,
坐在客厅里和朋友一起唱歌，
steel string acoustic, it's got metal strings on it,
钢弦原声吉他，上面有金属弦，
normal neck, it's about as wide as electric guitar neck, very similar to that,
正常的琴颈，它大概和电吉他的琴颈一样宽，非常相似，
it's a steel string, acoustic come in different sizes,
这是钢弦，原声吉他有不同的尺寸，
great guitar to have great guitar to play.
大的吉他，有大的吉他可以弹奏。
Okay, here I have a nylon string guitar,
好的，我这里有一把尼龙弦吉他，
you'll notice the body's a little bit smaller,
你会注意到琴体稍微小了一点，
it's got nylon strings,
它有尼龙弦，
its going to get a little bit of a sweeter sound,
它会有一点甜美的声音，
use it a lot for classical playing
经常使用它来演奏古典音乐，
as well as just good sweet guitar sound,
以及甜美的吉他音效，
okay, the neck is wider than a normal steel string acoustic,
好的，琴颈比普通的钢弦吉他要宽，
but it's a very pleasant guitar to have,
但这是一把非常令人愉悦的吉他，
I love playing my nylon string.
我喜欢弹尼龙弦。
Here's another type of steel string acoustic guitar, that you'll see quite a bit,
这是另一种钢弦原声吉他，你会经常看到，
this is a twelve string guitar,
这是一把十二弦吉他，
now normal guitar has six strings on it,
现在普通的吉他上有六根弦，
this one has twelve,
这把有十二根，
so each of the strings is basically doubled,
每根弦都是双倍的，
most of them with a string that's an octave above the one that you're playing,
大多数弦比你演奏的弦高出一个八度，
so you can play it still like a normal guitar,
所以你仍然可以像弹普通吉他一样演奏它，
a G chord, a C chord, D chord,
G 和弦， C 和弦， D 和弦，
the strings are so close together,
琴弦靠得很近，
that you can finger it almost like a regular guitar,
你几乎可以像拨动一把普通吉他一样拨动它，
it's a little bit wider,
它稍微宽了一点，
of course, with all those strings,
当然，有了这么多弦，
it's a little bit tougher to play,
演奏起来就有点困难了，
to put all those strings down,
把所有这些弦都放下来，
but it is has a very unique and interesting sound,
但它有一个非常独特和有趣的声音，
very ringy, very melodic sort of sound,
非常响亮，非常旋律的声音，
with all those strings, it's also louder,
有了所有这些弦，它声音也更大，
and physically a little bit bigger
体力上也更大一点，
to, to, to, to handle all of those strings.
来处理这些琴弦，
Okay, let's talk about a little bit of equipment,
好的，让我们来谈谈一些设备，
that you can use with your acoustic guitar.
你可以和你的原声吉他一起使用。
Now, there's a couple different types of pickups that folks use with acoustic guitars,
现在，有几种不同类型的拾音器，人们用在原声吉他上，
most often it's a piezo bridge pickup,
最常见的是压电琴桥拾音器，
which, it's a little strip of wire
这是一条小电线，
that is actually underneath your bridge,
在你的琴桥下面，
or sometimes it's even attached to your bridge
或者有时它甚至连接到你的琴桥上，
and they're all just one unit,
它们都是一个单元，
it just picks up the sound there through pressure waves
它只是通过压力波拾取那里的声音，
that are going through the top sound board of your guitar
压力波穿过吉他的顶部音板，
and usually comes out through your end pin here
通常通过末端出来，
and you can plug in the guitar that way,
你可以用这种方式插入吉他，
sometimes you'll even see pickups that are actually electric guitar pickup,
有时你甚至会看到实际上是电吉他拾音器的拾音器，
that they fit inside the acoustic guitar hole,
它们可以装在原声吉他孔中，
those aren't quite going to get you as natural a sound as a piezo pickup.
这些不会给你带来像 piezo 拾音器一样自然的声音。
The third way that that folks pick up guitars, electric or acoustic guitars is,
人们拿起电吉他或原声吉他的第三种方式是，
they have just a small condenser mic that's actually on the inside of the guitar,
他们只在吉他内部有一个小的电容式麦克风，
it can get real, get a very natural sound, get a very big sound,
它可以变得真实，得到非常自然的声音，得到非常大的声音，
often times you have one problem with them,
通常情况下，你对他们有一个问题，
it's a real common problem that you have with acoustic guitars, feedback,
这是原声吉他的一个很常见的问题，反馈，
if you're playing in any sort of situation that's loud
如果你在任何一种很大声的情况下演奏，
and there's a lot of sound around
周围有很多声音，
feedback from you or from other instruments and musicians on stage,
来自你或舞台上其他乐器和音乐家的反馈，
will get inside of your sound hole
会进入你的音洞，
to pick up is a pick up a bridge pick up here,
琴桥拾音器在这里，
so it's picking up anything that's vibrating the top of this guitar,
所以它可以接收到任何在吉他顶部振动的信号，
so if whatever's vibrating it,
所以，如果有任何东西在震动它，
no matter whether I'm doing this or whether whether I'm playing the guitar,
不管我是在做这个，或者我是否在弹吉他，
that's all being picked up through here,
这些都是通过这里被拾取的，
so once feedback starts in there,
所以一旦反馈开始了，
it just kind of it goes through here,
它就像是通过这里，
out my guitar, through my amp, back into my guitar
从我的吉他出来，通过我的功放，回到我的吉他，
and it just starts going and getting bigger and bigger, bigger,
然后它就开始变得越来越大，
one of the best investments you can make as an acoustic player
作为一名原声吉他演奏者，你能做的最好的投资之一，
is a little plastic or rubber device here called a feedback buster
就是塑料或橡胶设备在这里被称为反馈破坏器，
and there's different names for them
它们有不同的名称，
and it just fits right in your sound hole,
它恰好适合你的音孔，
and it stops the sound from going actually inside the instrument,
它会阻止声音真正进入乐器内部，
so any outside sounds from going in your instrument,
因此任何外部声音都不会进入乐器，
so you can still play your strings,
这样你仍然可以演奏你的弦，
and it's gonna be picked up through your bridge pickup right here,
它会通过你的琴桥拾音器拾取，
but it's not gonna be as susceptible to feedback,
但它不会那么容易受到反馈的影响，
is a great device,
这是一个很棒的设备，
that every acoustic guitar player,
每个吉他演奏者，
that's running through a band system or a sound system needs to have.
在乐队系统或音乐系统都需要的。
There are also effect units that you can get,
你也可以得到一些效果单元，
for acoustic instrument acoustic instrument processors,
对于原声乐器，原声乐器处理器，
You can in adjust your EQ,
你可以调整你的均衡器，
you can add some reverb, maybe some chorus,
你可以添加一些混响，也许是一些合唱，
very helpful units
非常有用的单元
to try and determine to try and get a little bit more out of your acoustic playing,
来尝试并决定尝试从你的原声演奏中获得更多，
especially if you're in a live situation.
特别是当你在现场的情况下。
Okay, your assignment for this session is like this,
好的，你这节课的作业是这样的，
you need to practice your sixteenth note strumming,
你需要练习你的十六分音符，
on open and with barre chords,
在开放和弦和横按和弦上，
use open chords, use barre chords,
使用开放和弦，使用横按节弦，
practice that sixteenth note strumming,
练习十六分音符扫弦，
start off slow,
开始的时候要慢，
slowly increase your speed,
慢慢提高你的速度，
remember those accents,
记得那些重音，
how we built down all the way down to that subdivision,
我们是如何一直往下构建细分，
where we left those ones out
我们剩下那些，
and we were just left with the accented notes,
我们只剩下带重音的音符，
that's where we're going,
这就是我们要去的地方，
good smooth strumming.
很流畅地扫弦。
Play the strumming exercises in your book,
演奏你书中的扫弦练习，
also, there's plenty of exercises in the Jam Along CDs,
此外， CD 上还有大量的 Jam Along 练习，
and there's extra songs in your book as well,
你的书中还有额外的歌曲，
experiment with, experiment with making up your own patterns,
尝试做你自己的模式，
don't just do the ones I have here,
不要只做我这里有的，
so I just have a handful of them down there,
所以我在下面只有几个，
make up your own patterns,
编造你自己的模式，
your own pattern will give yourself the unique sound that you need,
你自己的模式会给你自己需要的独特的声音，
and it doesn't take like a whole bunch of different patterns,
而不是一大堆不同的模式，
just find a couple that suits your playing style best,
只要找一对最适合你弹奏风格的组合，
and that will kind of start to define your rhythm playing.
这将开始定义你的节奏演奏。
Okay, we got a lot of things to work out at the workshop,
好的，我们在 workshop 上有很多事情要做，
I'll see you there.
我会在那里等你。
Okay, welcome to the workshop,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop ，
we're going to talk about strumming,
我们要谈的是扫弦，
let's review good strumming technique.
让我们回顾一下好的扫弦技巧。
Okay, our hand, our wrist is loose,
好的，我们的手，我们的手腕是放松的，
but we have a firm grip on our pick.
但我们牢牢抓住了我们的拨片。
Okay, well let's just do sixteenth notes,
好的，我们做十六分音符，
I fired up my metronome here
我启动我的节拍器，
and we just do sixteenth notes,
我们只做十六分音符，
no accents, just straight sixteenth,
没有重音，只有十六分音符，
get used to that loose wrist,
放松手腕，
on a G chord,
在 G 和弦上，
two, ready go,
2 ，准备，开始，
slow and even,
缓慢而平稳，
Remember, we did our accents,
记得，我们做的重音，
like our strumming pattern number six down there,
像我们的扫弦模式练习六，
let's practice that one real quick,
让我们快速练习一下这个，
ready go,
准备，开始，
down up, down up.
下上，下上。
Okay, now let's look at strumming exercise number one,
好的，现在让我们来看第一个扫弦练习，
using that pattern that we just did,
使用我们刚做的模式，
starts off with a G,
从 G 开始，
we'll do that for four bars,
我们将做四个小节，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
back to G,
回到 G ，
down up, down up, down, down up, down up, down,
下上，下上，下，下上，下上，下，
C, keep that hand going.
C ，保持那个手的移动。
Okay, now let's get a little bit more complicated with our chords,
好的，现在让我们的和弦变得更复杂一些，
okay, look at exercise number two,
好的，看看练习二，
we just have two bars of E starts it,
我们有两小节 E 开始，
let's do that same pattern,
让我们做同样的模式，
slow it down a little bit,
放慢一点，
and go from there,
然后从那里开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
another bar, F#m, A,
另一小节， F#m ， A ，
let's do it again, a little faster.
让我们再来一次，稍微快一点。
Okay, now let's look at that third exercise again,
好的，现在让我们再来看看第三个练习，
okay, I added some different chords with it,
好的，我加入了一些不同的和弦，
remember our two chords, our minor eleventh,
记得我们的二和弦，我们的小十一和弦，
let's try it, two, ready, go,
让我们试试， 2 ，准备，开始，
Em7,
Em7 ，
now look at that,
现在看看这个，
I just have two beats on each of those Em7 and Asus right there,
我只有两个节拍的 Em7 和 Asus 在那里，
now, how do I do that,
现在，我该怎么做，
my, my rhythm is a four beat rhythm,
我的节奏是四拍节奏，
so how would I handle that,
那我该怎么处理，
well, just just simplify it a little bit,
只要稍微简化一下，
I would go maybe down,
我可能会，下，
you could, it doesn't really matter what you do for those two beats,
你可以，你为这两个节拍做什么并不重要，
you do have to break that rhythm go,
你必须打破那个节奏，
you can just do two quarter notes if you want to,
如果你愿意，你可以只做两个四分之一音符，
or a couple of eighths
或者几个四分之一音符，
or a quarter and an eighth,
或者四分之一和八分之一音符，
doesn't matter,
没关系，
just whatever you can, as long as you break those two up,
只要你把这两个分开，
and when you get back to the measures that have four in them,
当你回到有四个的小节时，
you're back to your strumming pattern again.
你又回到了你的扫弦模式。
Okay, let's try again one more time,
好的，让我们再试一次，
ready go, top,
准备，开始，
see how that works for those particular two beats,
看看这两个特定节拍是如何工作的，
I don't necessarily have to stay with the rhythm,
我不一定要跟上节奏，
I can do whatever I want to for those two beats.
我可以做任何我想做的事情，对于这两个节拍。
There's more songs and more strumming exercises in your materials there,
你的材料里有更多的歌曲和扫弦练习，
don't forget the Jam Along CDs,
别忘了 Jam Along CD ，
give you a lot of good practice on strumming,
给了你很多扫弦的好的练习，
relax that wrist,
放松你的手腕，
and that will give you a good fluid strumming techniques,
这会给你一个很好的流畅的扫弦技巧，
keep up the good work as you're doing all this strumming stuff,
当你在做所有这些扫弦的事情时，继续做好工作，
there's a lot of good material that you can cover
有很多很好的材料，你可以涵盖，
and it really kicks up your plan,
它启动了你的计划，
it's a little tricky to get started with,
入门有点棘手，
but the more you do it, the easier it'll get.
但你做得越多，就越容易做到。
I'll see you next time.
我们下次见。